Guide to the Asian CineVision Records TAM.416
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Video Recordings
  - Video 343: CCTV, 1982-05-20; cuid33439 (Box 104)
  - Video 345: CCTV, 1982-05-24; cuid33441 (Box 104)
  - Video 344: CCTV, 1982-05-21; cuid33440 (Box 104)
  - Video 346: CCTV, 1982-05-25; cuid33442 (Box 104)
  - Video 347: CCTV, 1982-05-26; cuid33443 (Box 104)
  - Video 348: CCTV, 1982-05-27; cuid33444 (Box 105)
  - Video 349: CCTV, 1982-05-28; cuid33445 (Box 105)
  - Video 350: CCTV, 1982-05-31; cuid33446 (Box 105)
  - Video 351: CCTV, 1982-06-01; cuid33447 (Box 105)
  - Video 352: CCTV, 1982-06-02; cuid33448 (Box 105)
  - Video 353: CCTV, 1982-06-03; cuid33449 (Box 105)
  - Video 354: CCTV, 1982-06-04; cuid33450 (Box 105)
  - Video 355: CCTV, 1982-06-07; cuid33451 (Box 105)
  - Video 356: CCTV, 1982-06-08; cuid33452 (Box 105)
  - Video 357: CCTV, 1982-06-09; cuid33453 (Box 106)
  - Video 358: CCTV, 1982-06-10; cuid33454 (Box 106)
  - Video 359: CCTV, 1982-06-11; cuid33455 (Box 106)
  - Video 360: CCTV, 1982-06-14; cuid33456 (Box 106)
  - Video 361: CCTV, 1982-06-15; cuid33457 (Box 106)
  - Video 362: CCTV, 1982-06-16; cuid33458 (Box 106)
  - Video 363: CCTV, 1982-06-17; cuid33459 (Box 106)
  - Video 364: CCTV, 1982-06-18; cuid33460 (Box 106)
  - Video 365: CCTV, 1982-06-21; cuid33461 (Box 106)
  - Video 366: CCTV, 1982-06-22; cuid33462 (Box 107)
  - Video 367: CCTV, 1982-06-23; cuid33463 (Box 107)
  - Video 368: CCTV, 1982-06-24; cuid33464 (Box 107)
  - Video 369: CCTV, 1982-06-25; cuid33465 (Box 107)
  - Video 370: CCTV, 1982-06-28; cuid33466 (Box 107)
  - Video 371: CCTV, 1982-06-29; cuid33467 (Box 107)
  - Video 372: CCTV, 1982-06-30; cuid33468 (Box 107)
  - Video 373: CCTV, 1982-07-01; cuid33469 (Box 107)
  - Video 374: CCTV, 1982-07-02; cuid33470 (Box 107)
  - Video 375: CCTV, 1985-07-05; cuid33471 (Box 108)
  - Video 376: CCTV, 1982-07-06; cuid33472 (Box 108)
  - Video 377: CCTV, 1982-07-07; cuid33473 (Box 108)
  - Video 378: CCTV, 1982-07-08; cuid33474 (Box 108)
  - Video 379: CCTV, 1982-07-09; cuid33475 (Box 108)
  - Video 380: CCTV, 1982-07-12; cuid33476 (Box 108)
  - Video 381: CCTV, 1982-07-13; cuid33477 (Box 108)
  - Video 382: CCTV, 1982-07-14; cuid33478 (Box 108)
  - Video 383: CCTV, 1982-07-15; cuid33479 (Box 108)
  - Videos 384-392 ( inch videos), Jul 16-28, 1982; cuid1788 (Box 109)
    - Video 384 (Box 109, U-matic Video 384)
    - Video 385 (Box 109, U-matic Video 385)
    - Video 386 (Box 109, U-matic Video 386)
    - Video 387 (Box 109, U-matic Video 387)
    - Video 388 (Box 109, U-matic Video 388)
    - Video 389 (Box 109, U-matic Video 389)
    - Video 390 (Box 109, U-matic Video 390)
    - Video 391 (Box 109, U-matic Video 391)
    - Video 392 (Box 109, U-matic Video 392)
  - Video 393: CCTV, July 29, 1982; cuid36945 (Box 110, U-matic Video 393)
    Duration: 60 minutes.
  - Video 394: CCTV, July 30, 1982; cuid36946 (Box 110, U-matic Video 394)
  - Video 395: CCTV, August 2, 1982; cuid36947 (Box 110, U-matic Video 395)
  - Video 396: CCTV, August 3, 1982; cuid36948 (Box 110, U-matic Video 396)
  - Video 397: CCTV, August 4, 1982; cuid36949 (Box 110, U-matic Video 397)
  - Video 398: CCTV, August 5, 1982; cuid36950 (Box 110, U-matic Video 398)
  - Video 399: CCTV, August 6, 1982; cuid36951 (Box 110, U-matic Video 399)
  - Video 400: CCTV, August 9, 1982; cuid36952 (Box 110, U-matic Video 400)
  - Video 401: CCTV, August 10, 1982; cuid36953 (Box 110, U-matic Video 401)
  - Videos 402-410 ( inch videos), Aug 11-23, 1982; cuid1790 (Box 111)
    - Video 402 (Box 111, U-matic Video 402)
    - Video 403 (Box 111, U-matic Video 403)
    - Video 404 (Box 111, U-matic Video 404)
    - Video 405 (Box 111, U-matic Video 405)
    - Video 406 (Box 111, U-matic Video 406)
    - Video 407 (Box 111, U-matic Video 407)
    - Video 409 (Box 111, U-matic Video 407)
    - Video 410 (Box 111, U-matic Video 410)
  - Videos 411-419 ( inch videos), Aug 24-Sep 3, 1982; cuid1791 (Box 112)
    - Video 411 (Box 112, U-matic Video 411)
    - Video 412 (Box 112, U-matic Video 412)
    - Video 413 (Box 112, U-matic Video 413)
    - Video 414 (Box 112, U-matic Video 414)
    - Video 415 (Box 112, U-matic Video 415)
    - Video 416 (Box 112, U-matic Video 416)
    - Video 417 (Box 112, U-matic Video 417)
    - Video 418 (Box 112, U-matic Video 418)
    - Video 419 (Box 112, U-matic Video 419)
  - Videos 420-428 ( inch videos), Sep 6-16, 1982; cuid1792 (Box 113)
    - Video 420 (Box 113, U-matic Video 420)
    - Video 421 (Box 113, U-matic Video 421)
    - Video 422 (Box 113, U-matic Video 422)
    - Video 423 (Box 113, U-matic Video 423)
    - Video 424 (Box 113, U-matic Video 424)
    - Video 425 (Box 113, U-matic Video 425)
    - Video 426 (Box 113, U-matic Video 426)
    - Video 427 (Box 113, U-matic Video 427)
    - Video 428 (Box 113, U-matic Video 428)
  - Video 429: CCTV, September 17, 1982; cuid36954 (Box 114, U-matic Video 429)
  - Video 430: CCTV, September 20, 1982; cuid36955 (Box 114, U-matic Video 430)
  - Video 431: CCTV, September 21, 1982; cuid36956 (Box 114, U-matic Video 431)
  - Video 432: CCTV, September 22, 1982; cuid36957 (Box 114, U-matic Video 432)
  - Video 433: CCTV, September 23, 1982; cuid36958 (Box 114, U-matic Video 433)
  - Video 434: CCTV, September 24, 1982; cuid36959 (Box 114, U-matic Video 434)
  - Video 435: CCTV, September 27, 1982; cuid36960 (Box 114, U-matic Video 435)
  - Video 436: CCTV, September 28, 1982; cuid36961 (Box 114, U-matic Video 436)
    Duration: 60 minutes; Preservation note: Partial content loss around 55:00 minute mark due to tape damage.
  - Video 437: CCTV, September 29, 1982; cuid36962 (Box 114, U-matic Video 437)
  - Videos 438-446 ( inch videos), Sep 30-Oct 12, 1982; cuid1794 (Box 115)
    - Video 438 (Box 115, U-matic Video 438)
    - Video 439 (Box 115, U-matic Video 439)
    - Video 440 (Box 115, U-matic Video 440)
    - Video 441 (Box 115, U-matic Video 441)
    - Video 442 (Box 115, U-matic Video 442)
    - Video 443 (Box 115, U-matic Video 443)
    - Video 444 (Box 115, U-matic Video 444)
    - Video 445 (Box 115, U-matic Video 445)
    - Video 446 (Box 115, U-matic Video 446)
  - Videos 447-455 ( inch videos), Oct 13-25, 1982; cuid1795 (Box 116)
    - Video 447 (Box 116, U-matic Video 447)
    - Video 448 (Box 116, U-matic Video 448)
    - Video 449 (Box 116, U-matic Video 449)
    - Video 450 (Box 116, U-matic Video 450)
    - Video 451 (Box 116, U-matic Video 451)
    - Video 452 (Box 116, U-matic Video 452)
    - Video 453 (Box 116, U-matic Video 453)
    - Video 454 (Box 116, U-matic Video 454)
    - Video 455 (Box 116, U-matic Video 455)
  - Videos 456-464 ( inch videos), Oct 26-Nov 5, 1982; cuid1796 (Box 117)
    - Video 456 (Box 117, U-matic Video 456)
    - Video 457 (Box 117, U-matic Video 457)
    - Video 458 (Box 117, U-matic Video 458)
    - Video 459 (Box 117, U-matic Video 459)
    - Video 460 (Box 117, U-matic Video 460)
    - Video 461 (Box 117, U-matic Video 461)
    - Video 462 (Box 117, U-matic Video 462)
    - Video 463 (Box 117, U-matic Video 463)
    - Video 464 (Box 117, U-matic Video 464)
  - Videos 465-473 ( inch videos), Nov 8-18, 1982; cuid1797 (Box 118)
    - Video 465 (Box 118, U-matic Video 465)
    - Video 466 (Box 118, U-matic Video 466)
    - Video 467 (Box 118, U-matic Video 467)
    - Video 468 (Box 118, U-matic Video 468)
    - Video 469 (Box 118, U-matic Video 469)
    - Video 470 (Box 118, U-matic Video 470)
    - Video 471 (Box 118, U-matic Video 471)
    - Video 472 (Box 118, U-matic Video 472)
    - Video 473 (Box 118, U-matic Video 473)
  - Video 474: CCTV, November 18, 1982; cuid43236 (Box 119, U-matic 474)
    Duration: 60 minutes
  - Video 475: CCTV, November 22, 1982; cuid43237 (Box 119, U-matic 475)
  - Video 476: CCTV, November 23, 1982; cuid43238 (Box 119, U-matic 476)
  - Video 477: CCTV, November 24, 1982; cuid43239 (Box 119, U-matic 477)
  - Video 478: CCTV, November 25, 1982; cuid43240 (Box 119, U-matic 478)
  - Video 479: CCTV, November 26, 1982; cuid43241 (Box 119, U-matic 479)
  - Video 480: CCTV, November 29, 1982; cuid43242 (Box 119, U-matic 480)
  - Video 481: CCTV, November 30, 1982; cuid43243 (Box 119, U-matic 481)
  - Video 482: CCTV, December 1, 1982; cuid43235 (Box 119, U-matic Video 482)
  - Video 483: CCTV, December 2, 1982; TAM_416_cuid36963 (Box 120, U-matic Video 483)
  - Video 484: CCTV, December 3, 1982; cuid36964 (Box 120, U-matic Video 484)
  - Video 485: CCTV, December 6, 1982; cuid36965 (Box 120, U-matic Video 485)
  - Video 486: CCTV, December 7, 1982; cuid36966 (Box 120, U-matic Video 486)
  - Video 487: CCTV, December 8, 1982; cuid36967 (Box 120, U-matic Video 487)
  - Video 488: CCTV, December 9, 1982; cuid36968 (Box 120, U-matic Video 488)
  - Video 489: CCTV, December 15, 1982; cuid36969 (Box 120, U-matic Video 489)
  - Video 490: CCTV, December 17, 1982; cuid36970 (Box 120, U-matic Video 490)
  - Video 491: CCTV, December 20, 1982; cuid36971 (Box 120, U-matic Video 491)
  - Video 492: CCTV, December 21, 1982; cuid43628 (Box 121, U-matic Video 492)
    Duration: 60 min
  - Video 493: CCTV, December 22, 1982; cuid43629 (Box 121, U-matic Video 493)
  - Video 494: CCTV, December 23, 1982; cuid43630 (Box 121, U-matic Video 494)
  - Video 495: CCTV, December 24, 1982; cuid43631 (Box 121, U-matic Video 495)
  - Video 496: CCTV, December 27, 1982; cuid43632 (Box 121, U-matic Video 496)
  - Video 497: CCTV, December 28, 1982; cuid43633 (Box 121, U-matic Video 497)
  - Video 498: CCTV, December 29, 1982; cuid43634 (Box 121, U-matic Video 498)
  - Video 499: CCTV, December 30, 1982; cuid43635 (Box 121, U-matic Video 499)
  - Video 500: CCTV, December 31, 1982; cuid43636 (Box 121, U-matic Video 500)
  - Video 501: CCTV, January 3, 1983; cuid43637 (Box 122, U-matic Video 501)
  - Video 502: CCTV, January 4, 1983; cuid43638 (Box 122, U-matic Video 502)
  - Video 503: CCTV, January 5, 1983; cuid43639 (Box 122, U-matic Video 503)
  - Video 504: CCTV, January 6, 1983; cuid43640 (Box 122, U-matic Video 504)
  - Video 505: CCTV, January 7, 1983; cuid43641 (Box 122, U-matic Video 505)
  - Video 506: CCTV, January 10, 1983; cuid43642 (Box 122, U-matic Video 506)
  - Video 507: CCTV, January 11, 1983; cuid43643 (Box 122, U-matic Video 507)
  - Video 508: CCTV, January 12, 1983; cuid43644 (Box 122, U-matic Video 508)
  - Video 509: CCTV, January 13, 1983; cuid43645 (Box 122, U-matic Video 509)
  - Video 510: CCTV, January 14, 1983; cuid43646 (Box 123, U-matic Video 510)
  - Video 511: CCTV, January 17, 1983; cuid43647 (Box 123, U-matic Video 511)
  - Video 512: CCTV, January 18, 1983; cuid43648 (Box 123, U-matic Video 512)
  - Video 513: CCTV, January 19, 1983; cuid43649 (Box 123, U-matic Video 513)
  - Video 514: CCTV, January 20, 1983; cuid43650 (Box 123, U-matic Video 514)
  - Video 515: CCTV, January 21, 1983; cuid43651 (Box 123, U-matic Video 515)
  - Video 516: CCTV, January 24, 1983; cuid43652 (Box 123, U-matic Video 516)
  - Video 517: CCTV, January 25, 1983; cuid43653 (Box 123, U-matic Video 517)
  - Video 518: CCTV, January 26, 1983; cuid43654 (Box 123, U-matic Video 518)
  - Video 519: CCTV, January 27, 1983; cuid43655 (Box 124, U-matic Video 519)
  - Video 520: CCTV, January 28, 1983; cuid43656 (Box 124, U-matic Video 520)
  - Video 521: CCTV, January 31, 1983; cuid43657 (Box 124, U-matic Video 521)
  - Video 522: CCTV, February 1, 1983; cuid43658 (Box 124, U-matic Video 522)
  - Video 523: CCTV, February 2, 1983; cuid43659 (Box 124, U-matic Video 523)
  - Video 524: CCTV, February 3, 1983; cuid43660 (Box 124, U-matic Video 524)
  - Video 525: CCTV, February 6, 1983; cuid43661 (Box 124, U-matic Video 525)
  - Video 526: CCTV, February 7, 1983; cuid43662 (Box 124, U-matic Video 526)
  - Video 527: CCTV, February 8, 1983; cuid43663 (Box 124, U-matic Video 527)
  - Video 528: CCTV, February 9, 1983; cuid36972 (Box 125, U-matic Video 528)
  - Video 529: CCTV, February 10, 1983; cuid36973 (Box 125, U-matic Video 529)
    Duration: 60 minutes; Preservation note: This video was incubated
  - Video 530: CCTV, February 11, 1983; cuid36974 (Box 125, U-matic Video 530)
    Duration: 60 minutes; Preservation note: This video was incubated.
  - Video 531: CCTV, February 14, 1983; cuid36975 (Box 125, U-matic Video 531)
  - Video 532: CCTV, February 15, 1983; cuid36976 (Box 125, U-matic Video 532)
  - Video 533: CCTV, February 16, 1983; cuid36977 (Box 125, U-matic Video 533)
  - Video 534: CCTV, February 18, 1983; cuid36978 (Box 125, U-matic Video 534)
  - Video 535: CCTV, February 21, 1983; cuid36979 (Box 125, U-matic Video 535)
  - Video 536: CCTV, February 22, 1983; cuid36980 (Box 125, U-matic Video 536)
  - Video 537: CCTV, February 23, 1983; cuid43664 (Box 126, U-matic Video 537)
  - Video 538: CCTV, February 24, 1983; cuid43665 (Box 126, U-matic Video 538)
  - Video 539: CCTV, February 25, 1983; cuid43666 (Box 126, U-matic Video 539)
  - Video 540: CCTV, February 28, 1983; cuid43667 (Box 126, U-matic Video 540)
  - Video 541: CCTV, February 28, 1983; cuid43668 (Box 126, U-matic Video 541)
  - Video 542: CCTV, March 1, 1983; cuid43669 (Box 126, U-matic Video 542)
  - Video 543: Angel Island Poem, cuid1806 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 543)
  - Video 544: Asian American Dance Company, CCTV labeled "A-11", cuid1807 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 544)
  - Video 545: Asian Americans in the Performing Arts Commission on Civil Rights Hearings 26 Federal Plaza, 7/11/74, cuid1808 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 545)
  - Video 546 Basement Workshop: William's tape, 1975-1979; Cuid1809 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Cuid1809)
    This video documents two Cantonese-language musical performances. The first covers a photo exhibition by Chinese Americans of anti-Japan campaigns; the exhibition is accompanied by Cantonese folk songs. A clip of a Chinese old man's Cantonese folk song singing performance is included.
    Format: 1/2" open reel videotape: EIAJ Type 1, Duration: 31 minutes.
  - Video 547: Bok Choy Blues, cuid1810 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 547)
  - Video 548: Bo Fung/Joel Lee, cuid1811 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 548)
  - Video 549: CCTV 2nd year celebration, cuid1812 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 549)
  - Video 550: Cheng's case 10-2-77, CCTV labeled "A-3", cuid1813 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 550)
  - Video 551: Chinatown A Place Chin to Live, CCTV labeled "A-8", cuid1814 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 551)
  - Video 552: Chinatown Action for Progress presents CBS TV News Special "Misunderstanding" Part 1 2/5/74, cuid1815 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 552)
  - Video 553: Chinatown's Challenging Children WNET/Ch13 Eric Orner 51st state, cuid1816 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 553)
  - Video 554: Corrine and Shirley Interview (Practice tape at ACV), cuid1817 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 554)
  - Video 555: Corky Lee's Group/Kin Watt, cuid1818 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 555)
  - Video 556: Film Festival: Jenny (1978), CCTV labeled "A-6", cuid1819 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 556)
  - Video 557: Film Festival: Wong Sin Sang Arnie Wong's Animations, 1978, CCTV labeled "A-7", cuid1820 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 557)
  - Video 558: Hispanic Dance, CCTV labeled "A-2", cuid1821 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 558)
  - Video 559: Immigrant Story/Jo, cuid1822 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 559)
  - Video 560: Joann, cuid1823 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 560)
  - Video 561: "Sut Yung Ying Yee" Lesson #2: Transfer, Please, cuid1824 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 561)
    Produced by the Chinese Media Committee
  - Video 562: "Sut Yung Ying Yee" Lesson #6: What's Your Size?, cuid1825 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 562)
  - Video 563: "Sut Yung Ying Yee" Lesson #7: Do You Have Chicken Wings?, cuid1826 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 563)
  - Video 564: NBC TV News: Urban Journal Parts 1-4, 6/2-6/5, cuid1827 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 564)
  - Video 565: O.A.A. Demonstration at Bijou, 5/16/74, cuid1828 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 565)
  - Video 566: Plaza Demonstration, 2/19/76, cuid1829 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 566)
  - Video 567: Program Excerpt: Fern Lee Monologue, Jogi Interview, CPB hearing, CCTV labeled "A-5", cuid1830 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 567)
  - Video 568: Stripper 3/79, CCTV labeled "A-10", cuid1831 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 568)
  - Video 569: Textbook Racism, CCTV labeled "A-12", cuid1832 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 569)
    Produced by KQED
  - Video 570: Workshop Projects, CCTV labeled "A-1", 1977; Cuid1833 (Box 127, Video Cuid1833)
    This video includes an interview with Chinese American artists who participate in an exhibition at Washington Square Park, New York City, a chewing gum advertisement produced by the second session of CCTV Production and Performance workshop, a sit-com featuring miscommunication between Mandarin and Cantonese speaking families, and interviews with Confucius Plaza residents. Also included is an interview with Mr. Lo, the vice-chairman of Confucius Plaza co-op project. He introduces the history of building the Confucius Plaza which is under the Mitchell-Lama Housing Program. The episode also shows a situation drama which features dilemmas in a Chinese American family. The end of the episode includes clips of lectures during the second CCTV Production and Performance workshop.
    Format: 1/2" open reel videotape: EIAJ Type 1, Duration: 32 minutes
  - Video 571: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "A-9: (Chinese) Master Tape Ed: 8-32-78", cuid1834 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 571)
  - Video 572: Unidentified, CCTV labeled: (Chinese), cuid1835 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 572)
  - Video 573: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "Edit #1: 1) 3 (Chinese) 2) CPC, 3) GAC), cuid1836 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 573)
  - Video 574: Unidentified, cuid1837 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 574)
  - Video 575: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "Reel 2 Not Rewind 2/22", cuid1838 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 575)
  - Video 576: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "A-4", cuid1839 (Box 127, Half inch video reel Video 576)
  - Video 577: Annual Show, 3rd, CCTV, CCTV labeled "A16", cuid1840 (Box 128, Half inch video reel Video 577)
  - Video 578: Asian American Dance Theater, CCTV labeled "A-14", cuid1841 (Box 128, Half inch video reel Video 578)
  - Video 579: Asian American Dance Theater I + II, 2-16-78, CCTV labeled "A-29", cuid1842 (Box 128, Half inch video reel Video 579)
  - Video 580: Asian American Experience Reel #2: 1. Slide Show Stereotypes Corky Lee, Robin Wu, B. Chu, 2. Intermarriage, CCTV labeled "A19", cuid1843 (Box 128, Half inch video reel Video 580)
  - Video 581: Film Festival: Fu Ding Cheng, Flight of Ideas, While in Bad Light, Annie Wong, Cracking Up, Women's Rights, Cowboy Fade-Out, Automobile, CCTV labeled "A15", cuid1844 (Box 128, Half inch video reel Video 581)
  - Video 582: From Division Street to Here (I, II), CCTV labeled A27, cuid1845 (Box 128, Half inch video reel Video 582)
  - Video 583: CCTV labeled "Final (see inside)", cuid1846 (Box 128, Half inch video reel Video 583)
  - Video 584: Martha Panel Show (sample), CCTV labeled "A22", cuid1847 (Box 128, Half inch video reel Video 584)
  - Video 585: Workshop Project 2 Picnic 7/26, Final Tape, CCTV labeled "283", cuid1848 (Box 128, Half inch video reel Video 585)
  - Video 586: Unidentified (Chinese), CCTV labeled "A-21", cuid1849 (Box 128, Half inch video reel Video 586)
  - Video 587: Unidentified (Chinese), CCTV labeled "A23", cuid1850 (Box 128, Half inch video reel Video 587)
  - Video 588: Unidentified (Chinese), CCTV labeled "A24", cuid1851 (Box 128, Half inch video reel Video 588)
  - Video 589: Unidentified (Chinese) by CT Lui, CCTV labeled "A13", cuid1852 (Box 128, Half inch video reel Video 589)
  - Video 590: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "139', cuid1853 (Box 129, Half inch video reel Video 590)
  - Video 591: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "224', cuid1854 (Box 129, Half inch video reel Video 591)
  - Video 592: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "225", cuid1855 (Box 129, Half inch video reel Video 592)
  - Video 593: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "226", cuid1856 (Box 129, Half inch video reel Video 593)
  - Video 594: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "231", cuid1857 (Box 129, Half inch video reel Video 594)
  - Video 595: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "236", cuid1858 (Box 129, Half inch video reel Video 595)
  - Video 596: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "240", cuid1859 (Box 129, Half inch video reel Video 596)
  - Video 597: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "276", cuid1860 (Box 129, Half inch video reel Video 597)
  - Video 598: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "278", cuid1861 (Box 129, Half inch video reel Video 598)
  - Video 599: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "279", cuid1862 (Box 129, Half inch video reel Video 599)
  - Video 600: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "282", cuid1863 (Box 129, Half inch video reel Video 600)
  - Video 601: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "289", cuid1864 (Box 130, Half inch video reel Video 601)
  - Video 602: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "293", cuid1865 (Box 130, Half inch video reel Video 602)
  - Video 603: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "298", cuid1866 (Box 130, Half inch video reel Video 603)
  - Video 604: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "299", cuid1867 (Box 130, Half inch video reel Video 604)
  - Video 605: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "A28", cuid1868 (Box 130, Half inch video reel Video 605)
  - Video 606: Unidentified, cuid1869 (Box 130)
  - Video 607: Unidentified, cuid1870 (Box 130)
  - Video 608: Unidentified, cuid1871 (Box 130)
  - Video 609: Unidentified, cuid1872 (Box 130)
  - Video 610: Unidentified, cuid1873 (Box 130)
  - Video 611: Unidentified, cuid1874 (Box 130)
  - Video 612: Unidentified, cuid1875 (Box 130)
  - Video 613: Black and White Logo, cuid1876 (Box 131)
  - Video 614: Color Logo, cuid1877 (Box 131)
  - Video 615:AAFF 5/12, cuid1878 (Box 131)
  - Video 616:AAFF Arnie Masako, cuid1879 (Box 131)
  - Video 617:Even's Interview? Reaction Shot???, cuid1880 (Box 131)
  - Video 618:Al Stewart: Past, Present and Future, cuid1881 (Box 131)
  - Video 619: AAIFF 1989 16mm trailer, cuid1882 (Box 131)
  - Video 620:1988 Logo, cuid1883 (Box 131)
  - Video 621: Woo Art Asian Cine Vision Graphic Open ACV Presents: 20 Sec. Plus August 23, 1988, cuid1884 (Box 131)
  - Video 622: Woo Art International, Inc. ACV Opening 07/14/89, cuid1885 (Box 131)
  - Video 623: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1886 (Box 132)
  - Video 624: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1887 (Box 132)
  - Video 625: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1888 (Box 132)
  - Video 626: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1889 (Box 132)
  - Video 627: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1890 (Box 132)
  - Video 628: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1891 (Box 132)
  - Video 629: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1892 (Box 132)
  - Video 630: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1893 (Box 132)
  - Video 631: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1894 (Box 132)
  - Video 632: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1895 (Box 132)
  - Video 633: "Once Upon a Time in China 2" Trailer, May 13, 1992; cuid1896 (Box 133, U-matic 633)
    Duration: 3 minutes
  - Video 634: Street interviews, undated; cuid1897 (Box 133, U-matic 634)
    Person on street interviews asking if people know the difference between Thailand and Taiwan
    Duration: 11 minutes
  - Video 635: "Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1987, Commercial", cuid1898 (Box 133, U-matic 635)
    Duration: 1 minute
  - Video 636: CCTV labeled "Camera training tape", cuid1899 (Box 133, U-matic 636)
    Duration: 19 minutes; Preservation Note: This tape had to be spliced together from multiple sections
  - Video 637: CCTV labeled "CCTV logo master", cuid1900 (Box 133, U-matic 637)
    Duration: 9 minutes